About

I'm a computer engineer with ten years of professional experience. I'm specialized in all kinds of internet technology, including front-end and back-end. My major work is on web server build-up and maintain, planning project, schedule control. I incline to be a full-stack developer.

Experience

COMMSCOPE ARRIS RUCKUS, STAFF SOFTWARE ENGINEER - 2019/10 - NOW

- Maintain existing systems and functions, debug (JAVA, Ext.js)
- New function development (Angular, RxJS)

ZOEK INC., SENIOR ENGINEER - 2017/05 - NOW

<u>FunNow</u> is a service platform for real-time booking all kinds of entertainment, include massage/spa, fine dining & drinking, late check-in, lashes and manicure, Fun outdoor activities.

- Maintain the merchant system and website development, use PHP (slim framework)
 - i18n, SEO, GA Tracking, Facebook Pixel
- Develop new merchant system
 - Vue.js, Firebase + Web Push Notification
 - RESTful API with Golang(gin framework)
 - Use ElasticSearch to develop product and sell-time search
 - AWS Lambda for schedule cronjob

SAGACITY TECHNOLOGY CO., LTD., SOFTWARE ENGINEER - 2013/04 - 2014/07, 2015/07 - 2017/02

<u>QuizFun 考尚樂</u> which is a simulation test and learning platform with knowledge sharing as the core.

Management team with Scrum, built a development and test environment platform on AWS. participated in background function development, front-end automation process (Gulp), studied different technologies and import into our product:

- Use React.js to develop the question editing interface
- Use Vue.js + Vuex to develop PDF / Word file upload question transpose tool
- Use ElasticSeaech to improve search experiences

EATME CATERING CONSULTING CO., LTD., PRODUCT MANAGER - 2014/07 - 2015/06

Eatme 食我 is provide more than 2000 restaurant coupons or discounts in Taiwan.

Apply the Laravel framework to independently develop <u>Eatme official website</u>, including Front-end interface and back-end management functions, including

- Landing Page One page website, used to show the product features and functions
- Blog features articles and classified management, and front-end display
- Use a third-party payment API to sell EatMe Cards

COMPAL ELECTRONICS, INC., DESIGN LEADER - 2011/08 - 2013/04

Porting audio function on android. Design IPC (Inter-Process Communication) mechanism for transformer pad project and demo at Computex 2012.

ACADEMIA SINICA, SOFTWARE ENGINEER - 2007/01 - 2011/07

Digital archive system and Unencoded Chinese Character technology application development.

- Text source evolution (文字源演變), electronic stamp (電子圖章), e-card (電子賀卡) technology license to IQChinese Corp.
- Chinese character query (漢字查詢), e-card (電子賀卡) technology authorized to the WingNet Technology Co., Ltd.

Education

National Chung Cheng University - Master of Computer Science and Information Engineering, SEPTEMBER 2004 - JUNE 2006

Skills

• Proficient : LAMP, Git, JavaScript, Gulp, Sass, Vue.js, Slim Framework, Laravel

• Intermediate : Golang, Webpack, ElasticSearch, Node.js, React.js, AWS

Reference

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/soarlin/

Github: https://github.com/soarlin Blog: https://soarlin.github.io/



